const questions: Array<QuestionType> = [
  {
    question: 'גָּדוֹל',
    answers: ['groot'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'גָּדֹל',
    answers: ['groot'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'זָקֵן',
    answers: ['oud'],
    explanation: '(alleen van personen)',
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'חָדָשׁ',
    answers: ['nieuw'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'חָזָק',
    answers: ['hard', 'sterk', 'stoer'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'חַי',
    answers: ['levend', 'levende wezens', 'levend gedierte'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'חָכָם',
    answers: ['wijs', 'bekwaam'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'יָפֶה',
    answers: ['mooi', 'schoon', 'goed', 'prima'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'יָשָׁר',
    answers: ['recht'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'מַר',
    answers: ['druppel', 'bitter'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'קָדוֹשׁ',
    answers: ['heilig'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'קָדֹשׁ',
    answers: ['heilig'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'קָטֹן',
    answers: ['klein'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'קָרוֹב',
    answers: ['dichtbij', 'nabij'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'קָרֹב',
    answers: ['dichtbij', 'nabij'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'קָשֶׁה',
    answers: ['hard', 'moeilijk'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'רַב',
    answers: ['veel', 'groot'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'רָחוֹק',
    answers: ['ver'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'רָחֹק',
    answers: ['ver'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'רַע',
    answers: ['slecht', 'kwaad'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'רָעָה',
    answers: ['ramp', 'narigheid', 'een kwaad'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'תָּמִים',
    answers: ['geheel', 'gaaf', 'vol', 'compleet'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  }
]
const lesson7Vocabulary: LessonType = {
  id: 'lesson7-vocabulary',
  name: 'Les 7 – Woordenschat',
  type: 'woordenschat',
  active: false,
  questions
}
export default lesson7Vocabulary
